{"id":"2017_19","name":"Romans Lesson 192017_19","memoryVerse":"“Consequently, faith comes from hearing the message, and the message is heard through the word about Christ.” – Romans 10:17","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_19_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 11:1-10.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:1-10"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_19_3","questionText":"3. Explain Paul’s reasoning as to why God has not rejected the Jewish people. How do Paul’s testimony and Elijah’s experience strengthen his explanation?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_4","questionText":"4. What is a remnant? How is the remnant chosen?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_5","questionText":"5. What is the connection between grace and the elect?  How does that impact your understanding of election?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 11:1-10.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:1-10"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_19_6","questionText":"6. From verse 7, what did Israel seek? Why did they not obtain it? (See Romans 9:31-33)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"9:31-33"}]},{"id":"2017_19_7","questionText":"7. How do the following passages help you understand verses 7-10?  Isaiah 29:10-14","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Isaiah","verse":"29:10-14"}]},{"id":"2017_19_7b","questionText":"7.  Psalm 69:22-26","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Psalm","verse":"69:22-26"}]},{"id":"2017_19_7c","questionText":"7.  Matthew 13:12-15","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Matthew","verse":"13:12-15"}]},{"id":"2017_19_7d","questionText":"7.  John 12:37-43","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"John","verse":"12:37-43"}]},{"id":"2017_19_7e","questionText":"7.  Acts 28:24-28","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Acts","verse":"28:24-28"}]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 11:11-24.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:11-24"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_19_8","questionText":"  8. Explain Paul’s reasoning in verses 11-16. What good has come from Israel’s rejection?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_9","questionText":"  9. Without pressing the illustration too far, give in a few words about the point Paul made in verses 17-24. How does this passage address the boasting believer?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_10","questionText":"10. How has God demonstrated both kindness and sternness in your life? What have been the results?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 11:25-32.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:25-32"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_19_11","questionText":"11. What could “all Israel” mean? Which interpretation seems most likely based on what you know about God and His Word? (There are several interpretations.)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_12","questionText":"12. What will happen to Israel?  How can we be sure?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_13","questionText":"13. What do these verses reveal about God’s work and character? How do these truths comfort or challenge you?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_14","questionText":"14. How did God show mercy to both Jews and Gentiles? Explain in your own words why all people need the mercy of God.","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Romans 11:1-32.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:1-32"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_19_15","questionText":"15. What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_19_16","questionText":"16. Homiletics for discussion and administrative leaders: Romans 11:1-32.","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"11:1-32"}]}]}}}